Simple Electric Power Steering  by SimMchanics

You need following license:

-MATLAB®
-Simulink®,
-Simscape™,
-SimMechanics™,
-SimElectronics®  (This is used to only Motor model, so you don't need if you change Motor model.)

Files:

Simple_EPS.slx          ---  Simple Electric Power Steering model
Simple_EPS.pdf              ---  Documentation of Simple_EPS.slx
Simple_EPS_lib  ---  This folder include original library used in Simple_EPS.slx


Copyright 2014 The MathWorks, Inc.
